{
    "question": "Bantu nyusun kata-kata ne jadi klimat yg bner ya yang dimulai dri yg bergaris bawah sama bantu buatkan CONDITIONAL SENTENCE TIPE 2    arrange the jumbled words to form meaningful sentences,starting with the underlined words.\r\n1. phone-puppet-his-invite-the-I-number-my-see-Finto-know-will-if-show-to-I-at-place\r\n2. and-holiday-Bali-if-have-will-his-Lombok-long-go-year-Mr. Kukuh-family-to-they-and-this-a\u00a0mohon di bantu",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "1. If\u00a0 I know his phone number, I will invite Finto to the puppet show at my place.<br>2. If Mr. Kukuh and his family go to Bali, they will have a long holiday to Lombok this year.<br>Sorry kalau salah, baru pemula hehehe<br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "contoh-certia-bahasa-inggris-last-vocation-892",
            "question": "Contoh certia bahasa inggris \"last vocation\"",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "It&#039;s curious as we grow older, how easy it is to lose our sense of \ndirection, a sense of vocation, a sense of God&#039;s calling us to important\n things still to be done. Vocations are not just for the young starting \nout in marriage, a career, or religious life. There&#039;s another kind of \nvocation \u2014 a kind of \"late vocation\" \u2014 God&#039;s final call to a strong \nfinish. It is God&#039;s call to each one of us to grow old gracefully \u2014 full\n of grace \u2014 to grow toward Him.    \nGod calls us to respond heroically, like Saint Paul, pouring ourselves \nout like a libation until we can say: \"I have fought the good fight, I \nhave finished the race, I have kept the faith\" (II Tm 7).<span><br><br><br>INI</span>\u00a0?\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "combine-the-sentences-using-too-so-or-either-and-neither-1-d-745",
            "question": "Combine the sentences using : Too, so, or either and neither    1. Dogs\u00a0can't eat vegetables. Cats can't eat vegetables\r\n2. We haven't eaten yet. Father hasn't yet\r\n3. Mitha is not seventeen years old. I am not seventeen years old\r\n\r\nJawabannya yang Jelas ya :)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. Dogs can&#039;t eat vegetables. Neither can cats<br>2. We haven&#039;t eaten yet. Father hasn&#039;t either<br>3. Mitha is not seventeen years old. I am not either<br><br>setau aku begitu aja sih udah betul. mudah-mudahan membantu ya:)",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-soal-expression-of-suggestioun-478",
            "question": "Contoh soal expression of suggestioun? \u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "woman ; l think the weather is not friendly enough for us to do outdoor activites.<br>mam ; <br>narator ; what will the mam likely reply with?<br>a. enjoy your flight<br>b.let&#039;s go to the beach.<br>c. yes . we&#039;d better cancel our trip<br>d. l don&#039;t think l can attend the meeting<br><br>jawaban c<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-buatin-dialog-expresing-anger-untuk-2-orang-524",
            "question": "Tolong buatin dialog expresing anger :)\r\nuntuk 2 orang",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Everyone Has Bad Day<br>Sari\t: Hey, Rangga!<br> Rangga\t: What displeasure!<br> Sari\t: What? What happened, Rangga? Are you angry about something?<br> Rangga\t: Oh, I\u2019m very sorry, Sari. I was walking near handkerchief. You can wipe up your wet shirt.<br>Rangga\t: Oh, thank you, Sari. So, how was your day, Sari? Did something bad happen to you too? Haha I\u2019m kidding, Sari.<br> Sari\t: Actually, something bad did happen to me. It\u2019s still driving me mad until now.<br> Rangga\t: Oh, really? What do you look so insulted about?<br>\n Sari\t: It\u2019s my boss. He said that I can have a day-offs earlier but \ntoday he revoked what he said. I was planning on going for a vacation on\n my day-offs with my family. I am extremely displeased about that.<br> Rangga\t: I\u2019m sorry to hear that.<br> Sari\t: Well, everyone has bad day but if we still consider it positively, everything is going to be alright<br> Rangga\t: Yeah, I think you\u2019re right<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "A = <span>why are you scared?<br>B = i&#039;am sorry. i spoil your diary.<br>A = what?? why did you do that?<br>B = i didn&#039;t purposely. sorry<br>A = wether the sorry can repair all?<br>B = OK. i will replace your diary, but iam sorry<br>A = it&#039;s up to you. <br></span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-dialog-bahasa-inggris-tentang-expressing-threateningthrea-780",
            "question": "Contoh dialog bahasa inggris tentang expressing threatening/threat ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "A : Hey, when do you want to pay your debt?<br>B : I will do my best to pay it next week.<br>A : It&#039;s better for you to keep your words, otherwise Don Corleone will kill you\u00a0<br>B : DOn&#039;t worry sir, I will keep my words",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-pengertian-dari-direction-text-tolong-ya-aku-search-gak-n-672",
            "question": "Apa pengertian dari direction text ? tolong ya , aku search gak nemu-nemu niih",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "text yg menunjukkkan arah kali<br>direction kan arah/tujuan<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-describe-dengan-tema-my-beloved-home-386",
            "question": "Tolong describe dengan tema \"my beloved home\"",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "My beloved home<br><br>It is located in the central park. My home is the sweetest home on my complex. It has green roof which is made from special clay. Therefore it is always shining when the sun light rise in the morning.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "my home.. my everything.. even\u00a0my home not as huge the president home or a museums.. even my home don&#039;t as rich as the businessman home.. i love my home.. because my home protect me from the light of the sun , from the extreme weather , from the cold of the rain.. but i still love my home..home sweet home.. you&#039;re my protecter from childhood.. how bad you&#039;re you still my home... i called it my beloved home",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "arrange-to-a-good-sentences-1-realized-i-just-mistakes-919",
            "question": "Arrange to a good sentences !    1)\u00a0realized - I - just - mistakes - had - we - made -\r\n2) they - when - gone - arrived - had - we - already\u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Maaf saya hanya bisa menyusun yang nomor 2, semoga membantu ya :)<br>2) We had already arrived when they gone.<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "1. \"I realized mistakes we had made\" (saya menyadari kesalahan-kesalahan yang telah kita buat), or \"I realized we had made mistakes\" (saya menyadari bahwa kita telah melakukan kesalahan-kesalahan).<br>2. \"They had already gone when we arrived\" (mereka telah pergi ketika kita tiba), or \"We had alredy gone when they arrived\" (kita telah pergi ketika mereka tiba).<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-bedanya-conditional-type-1-2-dan-3-320",
            "question": "Apa bedanya conditional type 1, 2 dan 3 ???",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "if conditional sentences? beda tenses-nya, sama fact-nya",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Type 1 = Real / Present Conditional (terjadi sekarang)<br>Form = If + S + V1..., I + will + V1...<br>Example = If I have money, I will treat you<br>Meaning = it may/ may not happen. Jadi artinya bisa terjadi atau tidak.<br><br>Type 2 = Contrary to the present fact (bertentangan sama yang terjadi pada kenyataan)<br>Form = If + S + V2..., I + would + V1...<br>Example = <br>a. If I <u>had money,</u> I would treat you<br>b. If I <u>were</u> you, I would leave him<br>Meaning = <br>a1. I don&#039;t <u>have money</u>, so I dont treat you, or<br>a2. I don&#039;t treat you, because I don&#039;t have money<br>b. I<u>&#039;m</u> not you, so I don&#039;t leave him<br>(intinya kalau conditional 2, penyataan dalam v2, arti dalam v1)<br><br>Type 3 <br>Form = If + S + had + V3..., I + would + have + V3...<br>Example = <br>a. If I had had money, I would have treated you<br>b. If my father had got marred again, my mother would have killed him<br>Meaning = <br>a. I didn&#039;t have money, so I didn&#039;t treat you<br>b. My father didn&#039;t get married again, so my mother didn&#039;t kill him<br>(intinya kalau conditional 3, penyataan dalam v3, arti dalam v2)<br><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-text-hartatory-explenation-yang-berjudul-effect-of-insomni-716",
            "question": "Buat text hartatory explenation \u00a0yang berjudul effect of insomnia",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Effect of Insomnia<br>Horatory -&gt; thesis -&gt; reason -&gt; suggestion<br><br>Insomnia is kind of illness that makes people hard to sleep. Due to its negative effect, this illness is categorized as the dangerous symptoms. The reason could be classified from Internal feelings of the person. Therefore if we have this illness, better to have consultation toward the doctor. We stand to benefit by the greater time of sleep that we have.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}